<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FOSS on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/foss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FOSS on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress GPL drama...</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/blog/wordpress-gpl-drama.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/blog/wordpress-gpl-drama.../</guid>
      <description>After an argument broke out on twitter between [wordpress](http://wordpress.org&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank) co-founder Matt Mullenweg and Chris Pearson who created the popular wordpress theme [Thesis](http://www.pearsonified.com/themes&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank), an interview was put in place by Mixergy to talk to both of these guys and get their views on the matter.&#xA;Matt feels that since Wordpress is licensed th the [GPL](http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank), all themes would be considered derivative works, and therefore should also be licensed under the GPL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project or Masters</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/blog/project-or-masters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/blog/project-or-masters/</guid>
      <description>I had been planning to back to school to get my masters degree in Computer Science (or maybe Information Systems)&amp;ndash;Work would pay for the schooling as long as I made at least a B, and all of that would be well and good. However, it would take me 5 or 6 years to complete the program, and it would take up a lot of time.&#xA;I am now trying to decide if I would rather do that, or just undertake creating some project program or something on Linux for open source (or maybe for Android).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My top 5 Linux Distributions and runners up</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/blog/my-top-5-linux-distributions-and-runners-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/blog/my-top-5-linux-distributions-and-runners-up/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been running [ArchLinux](&lt;a href=&#34;http://archlinux.org&#34;&gt;http://archlinux.org&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank) on my desktop for a couple of years now, but these days I am getting on that computer less and less.  Little enough that I worry that my infrequency of system updates may cause some breakage.  To-date, I have not had any problems, but it could happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This desktop hosts pictures, and runs ssh, samba, and cups primarily.  So, I was considering hopping to another distro that would possibly be more stable and run for longer periods without a need for manual updates.  After some discussion on [identi.ca](&lt;a href=&#34;http://identi.ca&#34;&gt;http://identi.ca&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; target=&amp;quot;_blank), I think I will be fine staying with Arch, though&amp;ndash;I believe I can still manage to update once a month or so. :-)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I figure I will go ahead and re-detail my top 5 favorite Linux distros while I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about it, though. These are in order of my personal preference of use from past distro-hopping adventures:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
