<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Encryption on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/encryption/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Encryption on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:40:37 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/encryption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Proton Pass: A Guide to Secure Password Management</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:40:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-pass/</guid>
      <description>Proton Pass: A Guide to Secure Password Management In a digital world where security breaches are increasingly common, using a password manager is no longer just an option but a necessity. In this guide, we delve into Proton Pass, Proton&amp;rsquo;s answer to secure password management, offering you step-by-step instructions on setup, usage, and integration. For a broader look at Proton&amp;rsquo;s privacy-focused services, check out my previous post on Proton&amp;rsquo;s encrypted offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton Mail and other Services</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-encrypted-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:18:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-encrypted-services/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Proton and Their Suite of Privacy-Focused Services In an age where digital privacy is increasingly under threat, Proton has emerged as a beacon for those seeking secure communication and data protection. Starting with Proton Mail, the company has expanded its offerings to include a variety of tools designed to keep your digital life private and secure.&#xA;Proton Mail: The Heart of Proton&amp;rsquo;s Services Advantages of Encrypted Communication&#xA;Proton Mail is renowned for its end-to-end encryption, ensuring that your email content is secure from the moment it leaves your device until it reaches the recipient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPG Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/guides/gpg-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:50:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/guides/gpg-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>GPG Cheat Sheet I found this somewhere:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmessage</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/crypto/bitmessage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/crypto/bitmessage/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve started finding Bitmessage interesting again. I used it a little early on, but haven&amp;rsquo;t in a year or so.&#xA;After recovering my address, I&amp;rsquo;ve been back on the network and I&amp;rsquo;m remembering that I really like the idea of it&amp;ndash;mostly the simplicity! Compared to GPG, this is no contest that almost anyone could use this. Some people feel that GPG is damn near unusable, and while I don&amp;rsquo;t really agree, according to the guy in that talk I (and probably you) are considered the &amp;ldquo;technological elite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSH box</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/ssh-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/ssh-box/</guid>
      <description>Work has been very crazy for the past few weeks, so I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much of a chance to update this. Unfortunately I haven&amp;rsquo;t even had a chance to even play Minecraft. Although I did manage to log in and convert my local worlds to the new format, but that&amp;rsquo;s about the extent of it.&#xA;So a while back I received an eeePC 900a from a friend who owed me $25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>set up ssh  encrypted socks tunnel</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/set-up-ssh--encrypted-socks-tunnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/set-up-ssh--encrypted-socks-tunnel/</guid>
      <description>So I had started this a long time ago, and forgotten all about it as I really didn&amp;rsquo;t have a use for it. Now that I have the ability to tether, and I have my eeePC working again, combined with attending LUGs&amp;ndash;now I have the use for a secure tunnel.&#xA;In case you aren&amp;rsquo;t aware (I wasn&amp;rsquo;t), passwords and logins are sent in PLAIN TEXT&amp;ndash;yes, I said plain text. Nuts, huh?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
