<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 07:25:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Loop Incrementor</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/code/loop-incrementor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 07:25:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/code/loop-incrementor/</guid>
      <description>This code snippet is one that I made back in 2016. At the time, I was working on a lot of legacy VB6 code which was overrun with nested for-loops.&#xA;I started mocking up this loop-incrementor code to essentially make a sequence generator and get rid of the for-loops. This code was the simple idea behind a lot more complicated and elegant solutions I ended up using later.&#xA;Of course, this was just the first general concept, and it can definitely be improved upon in many ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cbr to Cbz Converter</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/code/cbr-to-cbz-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 07:18:01 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/code/cbr-to-cbz-converter/</guid>
      <description>As I continue to go through and find old stuff that I&amp;rsquo;d done, I found this one. I wrote this simple script a while back to convert some digital comic books into a format that I could read on my Kindle e-reader.&#xA;Download Source File:&#xA;cbr_to_cbz.py github gist: https://gist.github.com/jfrobbins/442a27f798219f78b3da #!/usr/bin/env python # Author: Jon Robbins # License: GPL3+ # based on the idea from https://trisquel.info/en/wiki/how-convert-comic-book-archives-cbrcbr-cbz # # This script recursively loops through directories below a starting point and converts all cbr file to cbz files # # requires: # - unrar # - zip/unzip # # gist: https://gist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pseudo randomness   my PRNG</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/pseudo-randomness---my-prng/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/pseudo-randomness---my-prng/</guid>
      <description>My wife sells stuff on Etsy, and occasionally does some giveaway type things. She&amp;rsquo;s been using random.org, which is a great TRUE random generator site&amp;ndash;however, many of their better services are not free.&#xA;I then took it upon myself to set up a pretty decent Pseudo-random generator that can do the things that she needs to do: mainly, enter a list of names and return one who would be the &amp;ldquo;winner&amp;rdquo; of the giveaway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Free and Open Source Software as it relates to me right now</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/thoughts-on-free-and-open-source-software-as-it-relates-to-me-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/thoughts-on-free-and-open-source-software-as-it-relates-to-me-right-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Free/Libre and Open Source Software (FOSS, or FLOSS, or F/LOSS) should be &amp;ldquo;liberally licensed to grant the right of users to use, study, change, and improve its design through the availability of its &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Source_code&#34;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo;  (&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Free_and_open_source_software&#34;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;).  &lt;a href=&#34;http://linuxoutlaws.com/explanation/foss&#34;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is another description from the Linux Outlaws page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The whole idea behind this, I believe, is the availablility and portability of the source code, as well as the freedom for users to modify and distribute the code as they see fit.  All well and good, I think&amp;ndash;definitely not a bad thing, and this is something I can support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The conundrum that I have is that for the past 4 or so years I have been programming almost exclusively in MS Visual Basic (classic, 6), with just a touch in C for micro controllers.  Only recently have we started the &lt;a href=&#34;http://factorq.net/2010/02/06/switching-code/&#34;&gt;conversion to PureBasic&lt;/a&gt;, which allows for us to compile cross-platform.  So what I am wondering is this: if I create some project using this language and free the source code with something like a GPLv3 license, would this even be valid since the compiler itself is not FOSS which could restrict distribution or other end-user freedoms and things of that sort? Would that be like the Mono projects?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If that would not &amp;ldquo;count&amp;rdquo;, or in the more likely case, if it would be shunned by the FOSS community I would rather not even waste my time.  In that event, I would much rather get out all of my old C++ books and browse some source code to brush up/re-learn what I have forgotten.  Or maybe learn Java, or Python, or&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This would be a much slower process, but if it is the &amp;ldquo;right way&amp;rdquo; then that is what I would have to do.   It isn&amp;rsquo;t like I even have a very good idea for a project anyway, just some &lt;a href=&#34;http://factorq.net/2010/07/03/project-or-masters/&#34;&gt;passing thoughts &lt;/a&gt;as arguments against going back to school&amp;ndash; So there is plenty of time for me to caught up, I am just impatient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the consensus here?  Is it wrong by the FOSS standards to use a non-open source compiler, for an otherwise open and free project?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>programs</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/programs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/programs/</guid>
      <description>Full running programs Please note the license and feel free to share and modify, just give credit where credit is due.&#xA;PB Declarations Creator tags: #&#xA;Published Date: Wed, 16 Jun 2010 17:03:30 +0000&#xA;Original URL | Original guid | PostID= 270&#xA;original filename: 109</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>snippets</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/snippets/</guid>
      <description>Code Snippets: I hope these can be useful to you, feel free to share.&#xA;Output HTML from 2D array &amp;lsquo;ByRef&amp;rsquo; Strings in PureBasic Published Date: Wed, 16 Jun 2010 17:05:44 +0000&#xA;Original URL | Original guid | PostID= 273&#xA;original filename: 110</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
