<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Server on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Server on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:53:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Five Minutes on a Server</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/guides/my-first-five-minutes-on-a-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:53:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/guides/my-first-five-minutes-on-a-server/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through some of my backups and came across this post that I (used to) use all the time.&#xA;I originally grabbed this a long time ago from plusbryan.com, but now it appears to be down&amp;hellip; so I&amp;rsquo;m glad I saved it.&#xA;my_first_5mins_on_a_server.pdf Thanks, PlusBryan, whoever you are &amp;ndash; this has saved me a lot of time over the years!&#xA;Here is the post in its entirety (made with a little help from grok):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>moving my pump home</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/server/moving-my-pump-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/server/moving-my-pump-home/</guid>
      <description>I was suspended from my vps again sometime yesterday due to going over my 3TB monthly bandwidth limit &amp;ndash; I was seeding many linux distributions, and with the fat pipes on the vps it just happened. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to be more careful in the future.&#xA;Anyway, this was a good opportunity for me to stop depending on the vps for my social networking at least, and I decided to go ahead and move my pump from the vps onto one of my home servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I got bored... so Creating a www server</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/i-got-bored...-so-creating-a-www-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/i-got-bored...-so-creating-a-www-server/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I had some time and then decided to do something I had always wanted to do: create an http server. I was using my desktop, which runs Arch of course, and went through several of these links and set my desktop up with Apache, PHP, and MySQL. Also, I installed vsftp as an FTP server.&#xA;I even signed up with DynDNS so that my dynamic IP can be updated to a (sub)domain and etc etc.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
