<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:32:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Distributed Social Network Anyway?</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/federation/what-is-a-distributed-social-network-anyway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:32:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/federation/what-is-a-distributed-social-network-anyway/</guid>
      <description>What is a Distributed Social Network Anyway? Ah, the digital age - where our lives are increasingly woven into the fabric of the internet. But let&amp;rsquo;s talk about a revolution, a shift away from the corporate giants that have, for too long, held our data, privacy, and freedoms hostage. I&amp;rsquo;m a Linux enthusiast, a FOSS advocate, and a firm believer in privacy and freedom. So, let&amp;rsquo;s journey through the landscape of distributed social networks, where I&amp;rsquo;m reminiscent of the old identi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Software Privacy</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/free-software-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:04:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/free-software-privacy/</guid>
      <description>privacy is impossible without free software I have this image from the FSF that I love: https://static.fsf.org/nosvn/posters/privacy-free-software-sign.pdf https://www.fsf.org/bulletin/2020/spring/privacy-encryption </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Five Minutes on a Server</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/server/my-first-five-minutes-on-a-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:53:08 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/server/my-first-five-minutes-on-a-server/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through some of my backups and came across this post that I (used to) use all the time.&#xA;I originally grabbed this a long time ago from plusbryan.com, but now it appears to be down&amp;hellip; so I&amp;rsquo;m glad I saved it.&#xA;my_first_5mins_on_a_server.pdf Thanks, PlusBryan, whoever you are &amp;ndash; this has saved me a lot of time over the years!&#xA;Here is the post in its entirety (made with a little help from grok):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPG Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/crypto/gpg-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 15:50:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/crypto/gpg-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>GPG Cheat Sheet I found this somewhere:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boglehead Investing</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/finance/boglehead-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:58:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/finance/boglehead-investing/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to do this particular post for a while. As a matter of fact, this is the main reason I&amp;rsquo;ve resurrected this website to begin with &amp;ndash; I wanted to document this for my kids, and for whoever else it is valuable for.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve found myself outlining this a few times, so why not put it on the internet? :-) Besides, it&amp;rsquo;s easy.&#xA;What is a &amp;ldquo;Boglehead&amp;rdquo;? A Boglehead is someone who follows the investment advice and strategy of John C Bogle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back 2 Bloggin</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/back-2-bloggin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 07:31:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/back-2-bloggin/</guid>
      <description>Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve resurrected this blog for better or worse. In the past, this blog has been many things over the years &amp;ndash; Octopress/Pelican/Jekyl/JBS, and before that Wordpress, and before that another homegrown system.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m actually not too sure how much content has come through, but it seems pretty old. Also I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that 1) my posts have not been great, and 2) I didn&amp;rsquo;t do the best job over the years of keeping things formatted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmessage</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/crypto/bitmessage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/crypto/bitmessage/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve started finding Bitmessage interesting again. I used it a little early on, but haven&amp;rsquo;t in a year or so.&#xA;After recovering my address, I&amp;rsquo;ve been back on the network and I&amp;rsquo;m remembering that I really like the idea of it&amp;ndash;mostly the simplicity! Compared to GPG, this is no contest that almost anyone could use this. Some people feel that GPG is damn near unusable, and while I don&amp;rsquo;t really agree, according to the guy in that talk I (and probably you) are considered the &amp;ldquo;technological elite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>moving my pump home</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/server/moving-my-pump-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/server/moving-my-pump-home/</guid>
      <description>I was suspended from my vps again sometime yesterday due to going over my 3TB monthly bandwidth limit &amp;ndash; I was seeding many linux distributions, and with the fat pipes on the vps it just happened. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to be more careful in the future.&#xA;Anyway, this was a good opportunity for me to stop depending on the vps for my social networking at least, and I decided to go ahead and move my pump from the vps onto one of my home servers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Federated Social Networks</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/federation/intro-to-federated-social-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/federation/intro-to-federated-social-networks/</guid>
      <description>Not very long ago there was an opportunity at the local LUG to volunteer to do lightning talks on some subject, and as a lightning talk is easier than a full-blown talk I decided to sign up and evangalize a bit on federated social networking.&#xA;I guess this subject is only tangentially related to Linux, but related enough to be interesting. The main point of federation is that it is encouraged for as many people as possible to run their own nodes&amp;ndash; this spreads the network around and makes it function well even if some portions of the network do get down (or are shut down).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
