<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accident on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/accident/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accident on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/accident/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wrecked my bike yesterday</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/blog/wrecked-my-bike-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/blog/wrecked-my-bike-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;410&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;I got up from the wreck, turned off the motor, checked my phone, tried to call my wife, and then took this picture&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_d4xnJM_h7n4/TJC4nEVqv8I/AAAAAAAAAL8/BZQzHMWE0zs/s640/IMG_20100914_120013.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/a&gt;[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I was coming home from work for lunch, and I downed my motorcycle.  I was actually turning into my neighborhood, so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going more than 40mph (probably more like &amp;lt;=30), and there was a large section of very fine gravel that I went through&amp;hellip;in the turn&amp;hellip;.as I was downshifting.  Basically it was all my fault, and it should have never happened.  But it did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was a left hand turn, but somehow the bike got slammed to the right.  I was thrown to the ground on my shoulder and head and elbow.  My hip hit shortly thereafter.  And I assume that as I was flung off, my left foot hi the handlebar or something, because my left ankle has a hematoma and is in quite a bit of pain.  My entire right side is very sore today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was wearing my standard gear: helmet (full face), textile jacket,gloves, jeans, racing boots.  If not for these things I would be in a whole new world of hurt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have scratches on my shoulder, and my shirt was torn (yes, even under the padded jacket).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My elbow has some roadrash, once again through the jacket.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I mentioned my ankle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My helmet has some scratching where it was impacted, and the visor broke off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My jeans were torn around the hip/right pocket area, and my DROID which was in that pocket has some scratching on its cover (the backside, luckily).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m just really sore today.  Otherwise I am fine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This really sucks because I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to sell the dang bike.  doh!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
