<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Proton on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/proton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Proton on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 08:24:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/proton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Proton VPN: A Deep Dive into Digital Privacy</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 08:24:18 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-vpn/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Proton VPN: A Deep Dive into Digital Privacy In the digital age, your online privacy is as precious as your physical security. Enter Proton VPN, a service designed by the privacy advocates at Proton to keep your internet activity secure, private, and unrestricted. For a broader look at Proton&amp;rsquo;s privacy-focused services, check out my post on Proton&amp;rsquo;s encrypted offerings.&#xA;What is a VPN? A Virtual Private Network (VPN) is essentially a service that creates a secure, encrypted tunnel between your device and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton Pass: A Guide to Secure Password Management</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:40:37 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-pass/</guid>
      <description>Proton Pass: A Guide to Secure Password Management In a digital world where security breaches are increasingly common, using a password manager is no longer just an option but a necessity. In this guide, we delve into Proton Pass, Proton&amp;rsquo;s answer to secure password management, offering you step-by-step instructions on setup, usage, and integration. For a broader look at Proton&amp;rsquo;s privacy-focused services, check out my previous post on Proton&amp;rsquo;s encrypted offerings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proton Mail and other Services</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-encrypted-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 07:18:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/privacy/proton-encrypted-services/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Proton and Their Suite of Privacy-Focused Services In an age where digital privacy is increasingly under threat, Proton has emerged as a beacon for those seeking secure communication and data protection. Starting with Proton Mail, the company has expanded its offerings to include a variety of tools designed to keep your digital life private and secure.&#xA;Proton Mail: The Heart of Proton&amp;rsquo;s Services Advantages of Encrypted Communication&#xA;Proton Mail is renowned for its end-to-end encryption, ensuring that your email content is secure from the moment it leaves your device until it reaches the recipient.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
