<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>M1911 &lt;Br&gt; on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/m1911-br/</link>
    <description>Recent content in M1911 &lt;Br&gt; on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/m1911-br/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Just a little test with a new toy</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/blog/just-a-little-test-with-a-new-toy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/blog/just-a-little-test-with-a-new-toy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After waiting for quite a while, the other day I finally got my first 1911.  It is a Rock Island Armory 5&amp;quot; Tactical model, sweet.  A little bit of history:  The [M1911A1](&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/M1911_pistol%22&#34;&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/M1911_pistol&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; target=&amp;quot;_blank) was designed by [John M Browning](&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Browning%22&#34;&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Browning&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; target=&amp;quot;_blank) and was the standard issue sidearm for the US military forces from 1911 to 1985 (and is still used by some US forces).  This model saw action in WWI, WWII, Korean War, and Vietnam War.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So anyway, I wanted to go break this thing in, and see what it can do.  I had some empty jugs laying around (2 milk, and one OJ), and decided to take these along.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After going through a box of 50 FMJ + one or two more magazines, I decided to try out the JHPs.  As anyone knows, JHPs (or Jacketed Hollow Points) are the way to go for defensive rounds, in order to attempt to prevent overpenetration and transfer as much inertia as possible.  The problem is, some guns do not like to feed them&amp;ndash;and 1911s are known to be particularly&amp;hellip;particular.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Test 1:&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;I lined up 1 OJ jug, 1 Milk Jug, and 1 pumpkin in a row on a fallen tree.  I loaded 1 Winchester White Box 230gr JHP round, and fired directly into the line.  The idea is to see how far it will penetrate, and (if we can find it) how much the JHP bullet will expand.  I crouched down to try to get a level shot, approximately 15 ft away from the target.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
