<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Years Eve</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/new-years-eve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/new-years-eve/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in my fq blog post, 2010 is coming to an end. Also, today is my son&amp;rsquo;s birthday! He turned 2 years old today, and for the next week or so, he and my daughter are the same age (then she turns 3, of course).&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m updating this blog from my chair, on my laptop, trying to catch up on LinuxOutlaws podcasts which I am listening to on my Droid phone (I am still at least 10 episodes behind).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2010 is coming to a close - Happy New Year</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/2010-is-coming-to-a-close--happy-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/2010-is-coming-to-a-close--happy-new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;2010 has really flown by for me and our family.  As always, the year has been packed full of events&amp;ndash;way too many to document fully, but I can sure try to sum upthe highlights here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Major events of 2010 that I can think of at the moment:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2010 Christmas</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/2010-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/2010-christmas/</guid>
      <description>It goes and comes like&amp;hellip;a cheetah. I definitely think this year has felt more like Christmas than the past few years&amp;ndash;maybe because the kids are really into it this year. And we have (slightly) more money this year than we have had the last couple. Either way, the kids saw snow (we have like 5&amp;quot; out there now, and supped to snow some more today), got lots of presents, saw lots of family, and absolutely had a blast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrecked my bike yesterday</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/wrecked-my-bike-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/posts/archive/wrecked-my-bike-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignleft&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;410&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;I got up from the wreck, turned off the motor, checked my phone, tried to call my wife, and then took this picture&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a href=&#34;http://lh3.ggpht.com/_d4xnJM_h7n4/TJC4nEVqv8I/AAAAAAAAAL8/BZQzHMWE0zs/s640/IMG_20100914_120013.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/a&gt;[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I was coming home from work for lunch, and I downed my motorcycle.  I was actually turning into my neighborhood, so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going more than 40mph (probably more like &amp;lt;=30), and there was a large section of very fine gravel that I went through&amp;hellip;in the turn&amp;hellip;.as I was downshifting.  Basically it was all my fault, and it should have never happened.  But it did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was a left hand turn, but somehow the bike got slammed to the right.  I was thrown to the ground on my shoulder and head and elbow.  My hip hit shortly thereafter.  And I assume that as I was flung off, my left foot hi the handlebar or something, because my left ankle has a hematoma and is in quite a bit of pain.  My entire right side is very sore today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was wearing my standard gear: helmet (full face), textile jacket,gloves, jeans, racing boots.  If not for these things I would be in a whole new world of hurt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have scratches on my shoulder, and my shirt was torn (yes, even under the padded jacket).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My elbow has some roadrash, once again through the jacket.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I mentioned my ankle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My helmet has some scratching where it was impacted, and the visor broke off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My jeans were torn around the hip/right pocket area, and my DROID which was in that pocket has some scratching on its cover (the backside, luckily).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m just really sore today.  Otherwise I am fine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This really sucks because I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to sell the dang bike.  doh!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
