<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jon Robbins (CC BY 4.0)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:15:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taco Soup</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/taco-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:15:13 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/taco-soup/</guid>
      <description>This is probably our most beloved dinner option. Delicious, easy to prepare, and with ingredients almost always stocked in the pantry, it&amp;rsquo;s a staple and a go-to.&#xA;Ingredients 1 lb ground turkey meat 1 can (15 oz) corn, no salt added 1 can (15 oz) dark red kidney beans, no salt added 1 can (15 oz) great northern (white) beans, no salt added 1 can (10 oz) Rotel 1 can (15 oz) pinto beans, no salt added 1 can (15 oz) black beans, no salt added 1 onion (white, red, or yellow, based on preference or availability), chopped 2 tbsp black pepper (modify to taste) 1 tbsp minced garlic (or substitute with garlic powder if necessary) 1 tbsp dark chili powder (modify to taste) 4 tbsp ranch dressing powder or one packet (or substitute with additional garlic powder or an alternate mixture) 4 cups (1 carton) chicken stock 1 tbsp crushed red pepper (modify to taste) 1 tbsp taco seasoning (modify to taste, add more as preferred) 1 cup sliced fresh mushrooms (optional) Notes:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sausage and Tortelloni Soup</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/sausage-and-tortelloni-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:08:01 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/sausage-and-tortelloni-soup/</guid>
      <description>Time: 35 minutes&#xA;Ingredients 1 tbsp olive oil 1/2 lb Italian sausage, casings removed 1 yellow onion, diced 2 cloves garlic, minced 1/2 lb carrots, peeled (optional) and sliced 15 oz can stewed tomatoes (with juices) 1/2 tsp dried basil 1/2 tsp dried oregano Freshly cracked pepper, to taste 3 cups vegetable broth 3 cups water 12-16 oz cheese or cheese and spinach tortelloni 1/4 lb fresh baby spinach (approximately 2 bags) Directions Brown the Sausage: Heat olive oil in a large pot over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beef and Broccoli</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/beef-and-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 09:02:15 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/beef-and-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2/3 cup reduced-sodium soy sauce 1/2 cup chicken stock 1/4 cup honey 2 tbsp rice vinegar 2 tbsp brown sugar, packed 3 cloves garlic, minced 1 tbsp cornstarch 1 tsp sriracha 1 tsp ground ginger 1/4 tsp red pepper flakes 1 tbsp sesame seed oil 1 pound flank steak, thinly sliced against the grain 1 tbsp olive oil 2-3 heads of broccoli, cut into florets 1 1/4 cup water Directions Prepare Sauce: In a medium bowl, whisk together the soy sauce, chicken stock, honey, vinegar, brown sugar, garlic, sesame seed oil, cornstarch, sriracha, ginger, red pepper flakes, and 1/4 cup of the water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shepherds Pie</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/shepherds-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 08:50:33 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/shepherds-pie/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1-1.5 lbs ground beef or turkey 1 cup onion, chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 (14.5 oz) can diced tomatoes 1 (16 oz) package frozen mixed vegetables, thawed 1/2 cup low-sodium beef broth 2 tsp Italian seasoning 1 tsp salt, divided 1/2 tsp pepper, divided 1.5 lbs baking potatoes, cubed 5 tbsp 2% milk Directions Preheat Oven: Preheat your oven to 375 degrees F.&#xA;Prepare Potatoes: Boil the cubed potatoes until soft, then mash them with the milk and half of the salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Pot Pie Casserole</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/chicken-pot-pie-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 08:38:30 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/chicken-pot-pie-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 lb chicken breast, cubed 12 oz frozen peas and carrots, thawed 1 onion, diced 1 can of cream of chicken soup 1 can of cream of mushroom soup 2 cups of frozen diced potatoes, thawed 1 cup of water 2-3 pie crusts (or crescent rolls) 1/2 tsp poultry seasoning (alternatively use): Garlic powder Pepper No salt seasoning (e.g., Mrs. Dash) A pinch of red pepper flakes Salt and pepper to taste (we omit salt as there should be enough in the soups) Directions Preheat Oven: Preheat your oven to 350 degrees F.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crockpot Red Curry Chicken</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/crockpot-red-curry-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 08:07:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/crockpot-red-curry-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Crock Pot Red Curry Chicken This is a recipe we enjoy frequently, especially during the colder months when soups are delightful.&#xA;Ingredients For the Crock Pot: 1 4oz jar of red curry paste 1 12oz can of light coconut milk 1 12oz can of regular coconut milk 2 cups chicken stock 2 tablespoons fish sauce 2 tablespoons brown sugar (optional - can be halved or omitted for less sweetness) 2 (heaping) tablespoons peanut butter 1 lb chicken breast 1 lb boneless, skinless chicken thighs 1 red bell pepper 1 yellow bell pepper (can substitute with green or red bell pepper, or banana pepper) 1 onion 1 can sliced bamboo shoots (optional) 1 can baby corn (optional) 1 heaping tablespoon fresh ginger, minced 1 cup frozen vegetables (like peas, or a peas/green beans mix, or just green beans) 1 tablespoon lime juice (juice from 1 lime) Cilantro for garnish For the Side: Cooked rice (we prefer basmati brown rice) Instructions: Prepare the Chicken: Cut both the chicken breast and thighs into thin strips, about 1 1/2 inches long.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overnight Oats</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/overnight-oats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 08:01:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/overnight-oats/</guid>
      <description>Overnight Oats Recipe Nutrition per serving:&#xA;Calories: 475 Protein: 26g Ingredients: 1 small mason jar 1/3 cup rolled oats 2 teaspoons chia seeds 1 teaspoon honey, maple syrup, or agave 1 tablespoon peanut butter 1/2 scoop vanilla whey protein powder 1/2 banana, thinly sliced 1/2 cup almond milk Steps: Combine Ingredients: Place all the ingredients into the mason jar.&#xA;Seal the Jar: Secure the lid tightly on the jar.&#xA;Mix Well: Shake the jar vigorously to ensure all ingredients are well mixed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Pie</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/apple-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:38:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/apple-pie/</guid>
      <description>Apple Pie Recipe Source: My Home Cooking&#xA;Apple Pie Crust Ingredients:&#xA;2 cups all-purpose flour 1 teaspoon salt 1 tablespoon sugar 6 tablespoons butter 6 tablespoons shortening 6 to 8 tablespoons ice water Utensils:&#xA;1 Mixing Bowl Rolling pin Knife Measuring spoons Measuring Cups Dough Blender Cutting Board 9-inch Pie Pan (smaller is ok, but no bigger) Instructions for Pie Crust:&#xA;First Step: Mixing the Pie Crust Ingredients&#xA;Warm the butter in the microwave until it is soft, but not melted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Cooker Thai Chicken Soup</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/slow-cooker-thai-chicken-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:28:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/slow-cooker-thai-chicken-soup/</guid>
      <description>Slow Cooker Thai Chicken Soup Source: foodiecrush.com&#xA;Ingredients:&#xA;2 pounds boneless, skinless chicken breasts or thighs 1 tablespoon olive oil 1 onion, chopped 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 tablespoon fresh ginger, grated 1 red bell pepper, diced 1 jalapeño pepper, seeded and finely chopped (optional for heat) 3 tablespoons red Thai curry paste (I usually use the entire small jar) 1 can (14 ounces) coconut milk 4 cups chicken broth 2 tablespoons fish sauce 1 tablespoon brown sugar Juice from 1 lime 8 ounces mushrooms, sliced 2 cups baby spinach or kale Cilantro for garnish Green onions, sliced, for garnish Lime wedges for serving Instructions:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Egg Casserole</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/breakfast-egg-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:16:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/breakfast-egg-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast Casserole With Sausage and Peppers I received this recipe from a friend, and it sounds good.&#xA;Source: bonappetit.com&#xA;Ingredients: 1 pound hot and/or sweet Italian sausage, casings removed 2 medium red bell peppers, stemmed, seeded, and thinly sliced 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil 1 large onion, thinly sliced 6 garlic cloves, thinly sliced 8 large eggs 2 cups whole milk 2 teaspoons kosher salt 2 teaspoons freshly ground black pepper 1 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes (optional for heat) 10 cups 1-inch pieces country-style white or sourdough bread (about 1 loaf) 2 cups coarsely grated Fontina or Gruyère cheese 1/2 cup finely grated Pecorino or Parmesan cheese Directions: Cook the Sausage and Peppers:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Deviled Eggs Recipe</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/classic-deviled-eggs-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:19:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/classic-deviled-eggs-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Classic Deviled Eggs I started with this recipe from Southern Living. With our chickens laying a plethora of eggs, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making deviled eggs a lot lately for functions, tweaking the recipe to my liking.&#xA;Ingredients: 12 large eggs 4 to 6 tablespoons mayonnaise 4 teaspoons spicy brown mustard 2 to 3 teaspoons pepper Paprika (optional, but not really) Instructions: Cook Eggs (Martha Stewart Method):&#xA;Place eggs in a single layer at the bottom of a pot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
