<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on jrobb.org</title>
    <link>https://jrobb.org/tags/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on jrobb.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:16:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jrobb.org/tags/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Egg Casserole</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/breakfast-egg-casserole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 10:16:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/breakfast-egg-casserole/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast Casserole With Sausage and Peppers I received this recipe from a friend, and it sounds good.&#xA;Source:&#xA;https://www.bonappetit.com/recipe/breakfast-casserole Ingredients: 1 pound hot and/or sweet Italian sausage, casings removed 2 medium red bell peppers, stemmed, seeded, and thinly sliced 2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil 1 large onion, thinly sliced 6 garlic cloves, thinly sliced 8 large eggs 2 cups whole milk 2 teaspoons kosher salt 2 teaspoons freshly ground black pepper 1 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes (optional for heat) 10 cups 1-inch pieces country-style white or sourdough bread (about 1 loaf) 2 cups coarsely grated Fontina or Gruyère cheese 1/2 cup finely grated Pecorino or Parmesan cheese Directions: Cook the Sausage and Peppers:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Deviled Eggs Recipe</title>
      <link>https://jrobb.org/recipes/classic-deviled-eggs-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 09:19:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jrobb.org/recipes/classic-deviled-eggs-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Classic Deviled Eggs I started with this recipe from Southern Living. With our chickens laying a plethora of eggs, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making deviled eggs a lot lately for functions, tweaking the recipe to my liking.&#xA;Ingredients: 12 large eggs 4 to 6 tablespoons mayonnaise 4 teaspoons spicy brown mustard 2 to 3 teaspoons pepper Paprika (optional, but not really) Instructions: Cook Eggs (Martha Stewart Method):&#xA;Place eggs in a single layer at the bottom of a pot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
